altcointrader.co.za 2016-04-20

# AltCoinTrader trading Privacy policy

## Your privacy is important to us

At AltCoinTrader we are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.We take this very seriously so that you may feel safe when trusting us with your confidentialy.

This policy (together with our terms and conditions and any other documents referred to in it) sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it.

We keep certain basic information when you visit our website and recognise the importance of keeping that information secure and letting you know what we will do with it.

For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998 (the Act), the data controller is AltCoinTrader.  
This policy only applies to our site. If you leave our site via a link or otherwise, you will be subject to the policy of that website provider. We have no control over that policy or the terms of the website and you should check their policy before continuing to access the site.

## Information we may collect from you

We may collect and process the following data about you:

  * Information that you provide by filling in forms on our site. This includes information provided at the time of registering to use or trade on our site, subscribing to our service or requesting further services. We may also ask you for information when you report a problem with our site.
  * If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence.
  * We may also ask you to complete surveys that we use for research purposes, although you do not have to respond to them.
  * Details of your visits to our site including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs, operating system, browser usage and other communication data, whether this is required for our own billing purposes or otherwise and the resources that you access.

## IP addresses, sessions and cookies

We may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration.This is statistical and security data about our users' browsing actions.

Your session activities are tracked! Most actions performed on our site and logged for security reasons!

We may obtain information about your general internet usage by using a cookie file which is stored on the hard drive of your computer. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer's hard drive. They help us to improve our site and to deliver a better and more personalised service. 

They enable us:

  * To estimate our audience size and usage pattern.
  * To store information about your preferences, and so allow us to customise our site according to your individual interests.
  * To speed up your searches.
  * To recognise you when you return to our site. 

You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the setting of cookies. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our site. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system may issue cookies when you log on to our site.

## Where we store your personal data

The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside South Africa. It may also be processed by staff operating outside South Africa who work for us or for one of our suppliers. Such staff maybe engaged in, among other things, the fulfilment of your order, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy. 

All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. Any payment or trade transactions will be encrypted. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone or to use that password for other sites or services as they might not keep that password secure and an insecure password could put you at risk!

AltCoinTrader has made every effort to ensure our site is safe and secure. In addition to this we make use of a Thawte Security Certificate to ensure all data is encrypted, however the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to to prevent unauthorised access. 

## Uses made of the information

We use information held about you in the following ways:

  * To provide security and to aid us with fraud prevention.
  * To ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer. 
  * To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes. 
  * To carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us.
  * To allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so.

## Disclosure of your information

We will not disclose your personal information to third parties:

Unless we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of security, fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

Our site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates.  If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies.  Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites. 

## Access to information

The Act gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act. Any access request may be subject to a fee of R 300 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.

## Changes to our privacy policy

Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page!  
The trader or user of the site has the responsibility to ensure that they have read and understand our privacy policy before trading or using our site!

## Our promise to you:

We at AltCoinTrader undertake to run our operation with honesty and integrity. We undertake to  act in a reasonable manor and deliver to our clients the highest level of service!
